<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Project name="3Head">
	<Package name="3Head">

		<Container name="Big Tasks">
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_MAIN_TITLE">
				<Original>Main Tasks</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_MAIN_DESC">
				<Original>These are the main objectives of Task Force Naga in the Area of Operation.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="STR_TASK_SIDE_TITLE">
				<Original>Side Tasks</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_SIDE_DESC">
				<Original>The tasks are optional, but are very beneficial for collecting intelligence.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="STR_TASK_GENERAL_TITLE">
				<Original>The General</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_GENERAL_DESC">
				<Original>
&lt;img image='data\general.paa' width='300' height='150'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Atonio Bole, nicknamed “The General”, is the leader of the Syndikat on the Horizon Islands.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
The government has been trying to nullify his influence on the islands to no avail.
Bole is smart, he's a veteran of many wars and has always been two moves ahead of local authorities.
When the island fell into Syndikat's hands, he knew where and when to strike, he sees what's in front of him and always thinks ahead.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
While he appears on some “promotional” footage of the Syndikat, Bole has proven to be extremely evasive whenever the HIDF had his location pinned.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Despite it being public knowledge that he is the leader of the Syndikat, the HIDF and local authorities are unable to truly link him to any of the actions he has taken against our sovereign.
                </Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_WARLORD_TITLE">
				<Original>The Warlord</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_WARLORD_DESC">
				<Original>			
&lt;img image='data\warlord.paa' width='300' height='150'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Second to the General is Ruru Babitu, or “The Warlord”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
He is the most prominent figure of the Syndikat and appears in most if not all of the footage that the Syndikat have published. Executions, beheadings, whatever gruesome message the Syndikat wants to send to the world, he's in it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Unlike Bole, Babitu doesn't possess the clever disposition of his superior. He's more action than he is brain. Babitu has also been noted to be extremely volatile and unwary of the consequences of his violent actions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Babitu possesses a golden Desert Eagle that he carries everywhere.
				</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_DEALER_TITLE">
				<Original>The Dealer</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_DEALER_DESC">
				<Original>
&lt;img image='data\dealer.paa' width='300' height='150'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
If we want to talk about real shadows, look no further than Lucas Umaga, or “The Dealer”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
The HIDF has profiled Umaga to be the logistics behind Bole's lofty ambitions in Pulau Monyet. He sources everything from weapons, vehicles and even Bole's spending power.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Umaga and Bole have had a long working relationship and the former is instrumental in the entire operation on the island, the HIDF has classified him as the highest priority target for kill or capture, though this is at the discretion of the deployed squads.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
No one knows where he is, or from whom he gets his equipment from. We've only seen him once wearing a blue cap. The people closest to him are also get first pick of newly acquired equipment, trying to seize Umaga will be a challenge, so be advised - proceed with caution when dealing with him.
				</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_JOURNO_TITLE">
				<Original>Rescue Journalists</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_JOURNO_DESC">
				<Original>
&lt;img image='data\journo.paa' width='300' height='150'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
The French government has reached out to inform us of two French nationals taken hostage by the Syndikat. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Both work for AAN World News in Paris and were in Horizon Islands for journalistic investigation around Horizon Islands and the local Syndikat takeover.
Unfortunately, they dug their noses too deep into the rabbit hole.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
The journalists are named Henry Kilian and Hortense Henrique. We're unsure where the Syndikat is keeping them, but priority is to locate and rescue.
				</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="STR_TASK_LOCATE_TITLE">
				<Original>Locate</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="STR_TASK_GENERAL_LOCATE_DESCRIPTION">
				<Original>Locate the general by collecting intel that may lead to his position.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_WARLORD_LOCATE_DESCRIPTION">
				<Original>Locate the warlord by collecting intel that may lead to his position.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_DEALER_LOCATE_DESCRIPTION">
				<Original>Locate the dealer by collecting intel that may lead to his position.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_JOURNO_LOCATE_DESCRIPTION">
				<Original>Locate the journalists by collecting intel that may lead to their position.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
		</Container>

		<Container name="Small Tasks">
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_INFORMANT_TITLE">
				<Original>Talk to Informant</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_INFORMANT_DESC">
				<Original>An informant who knows about Syndikat movements is in Tinobu. Meet him and see what he has to say.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CAMP_TITLE">
				<Original>Raid Camp</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CAMP_DESC">
				<Original>Intel indicates a Syndikat camp at this position. Raid it and collect more intel.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_AAA1_TITLE">
				<Original>Destroy AAA</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_AAA1_DESC">
				<Original>An AAA site was spotted on the south of Pulau Monyet in an old WW2 bunker. This AAA site has been harassing aircraft flying in and out of Monyet airfield and must be destroyed immediately.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_ARTI1_TITLE">
				<Original>Destroy Artillery</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_ARTI1_DESC">
				<Original>An artillery position was spotted on Mandomai. This artillery site is thought to be the main one harassing friendly forces, it's destruction is a priority.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CACHE_TITLE">
				<Original>Destroy Cache</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CACHE1_DESC">
				<Original>Intel revealed an ammo cache in a warehouse at Kambani. Destroy it to weaken Syndikat.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CACHE2_DESC">
				<Original>Intel indicates an ammo cache in a warehouse near Monse. Destroy it to weaken Syndikat.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CRASH_TITLE">
				<Original>Rescue Crew</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_CRASH_DESC">
				<Original>A friendly huey with 2 crew went down somewhere in the swamp at grid 0405. Their exact location is unknown, locate the crash site and extract the crew.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_POW_TITLE">
				<Original>Rescue POWs</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_POW1_DESC">
				<Original>New intel revealed that the Syndikat are holding a POW in a house at Jaya. Raid the position and extract as many POWs as possible. Syndikat are ruthless and will likely execute them if you aren't stealthy.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_POW2_DESC">
				<Original>New intel revealed that the Syndikat are holding 2 POWs in a the mayors old home near the airfield. Assault the building and extract as many POWs as possible. Syndikat are ruthless and will likely execute them if you aren't stealthy.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_KILL_TITLE">
				<Original>Kill/Capture</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_DEALER_KILL_DESC">
				<Original>Intel shows that a meeting between CSAT and Syndikat will be going down at the old hotel and that the dealer will be there. Bust the meeting and kill/capture the dealer.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_WARLORD_KILL_DESC">
				<Original>Phone records indicate that the warlord is hiding out on a hilltop base at grid 0508 with what appears to be a platoon sized force accompanying him. Conduct an assault on the position and kill/capture him.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_GENERAL_KILL_DESC">
				<Original>New intel shows the the general may be hiding in an old Japanese underground bunker near the airfield. It's exact location is unknown. Search for the bunker enterance and kill/capture the general.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_JOURNO_RESCUE_TITLE">
				<Original>Rescue</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TASK_JOURNO_RESCUE_DESC">
				<Original>Phone records show that the journalists may be being held in a warehouse on the east coast. Raid the position and bring the journalists to safety.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
		</Container>

		<Container name="DIARY">
			<Key ID="STR_DIARY_BRIEFING_TITLE">
				<Original>Briefing</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_DIARY_BRIEFING_DESC">
				<Original>
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;SITUATION&lt;/font&gt;     
&lt;br/&gt;  
The horizon islands are in a bloody civil war as the ruthless gang-turned-insurgency, Syndikat has challenged government troops on the islands on Tanoa.  
Recently however, they have made a move on Pulau Gurun and Pulau Monyet, islands previously known for their relative safety and tourism industry in contrast to Tanoa.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
Syndikat captured most of towns and villages on the islands, killing natives and tourists as they went. They managed to corner the small garrison of Horizon Island Defense Forces (HIDF) troops to areas around the Airfield, Tabako and Seliu.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
As for how Syndikat managed to pull of such an operation is unknown as they are typically poorly funded and organized. NATO suspects foreign involvement.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;     
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;ENEMY&lt;/font&gt;     
&lt;br/&gt;   
Syndikat can be identified by wearing a jungle uniform most of the time, but have been known to wear civilian clothing as well.   
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
Syndikat usually operate civilian vehicles or technicals, but have been seen with BRDMs and BTRs lately.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  
The ROE is loose, anyone with a weapon can be considered hostile.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;     
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;MISSION&lt;/font&gt;     
&lt;br/&gt;   
The goal of the main HIDF garrisons is to hold their current positions as the Syndikat resistance in the towns and villages is greater than expected.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    
You however, a member of Task Force Naga, a force created to fight fire with fire. Your goal is to disrupt Syndikat by collecting intel, conducting special operations behind enemy lines and dismantling their command structure.
				</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_DIARY_TUTORIAL_TITLE">
				<Original>Tutorial</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_DIARY_TUTORIAL_DESC">
				<Original>
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;INTEL&lt;/font&gt;      
&lt;br/&gt;   
One of the main mechanics of this mission is the intel system. In order to recieve new tasks you must submit intel. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
Intel can be found in the form of inventory items such as cellphones, documents, etc in the inventories of enemy units. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
In order to submit any intel you have collected, you must have the intel on your person and scroll on one of the laptops at your various spawn points to submit.  
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
Intel can also be obtain though talking to civilians. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;SLEEPING&lt;/font&gt;      
&lt;br/&gt;   
You can sleep by scrolling on the map board at FOB Seliu. All players must be in the vicinity of a spawn point or a camp in order to skip time successfully. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
&lt;font face='PuristaBold' color='#fce300' size='15'&gt;PORTABLE SPAWNS&lt;/font&gt;      
&lt;br/&gt;   
You can create new spawn points on the map by getting the camping tent from an arsenal and placing it using the scroll wheel. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   
Once placed, you will be able to sleep and fast travel using the tent.
				</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
		</Container>

		<Container name="TALK">
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_INFORMANT">
				<Original>Talk to Informant</Original>
				<Russian>I know of some important Syndikat positions with big weapons. Here, I'll mark them on your map.</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK">
				<Original>Talk</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW1">
				<Original>I dont know anything man.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW2">
				<Original>Sorry, can't help you.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW3">
				<Original>I dont know anything.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW4">
				<Original>Cant help, sorry.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW5">
				<Original>I dont have any information for you.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW6">
				<Original>Fuck off man.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONTKNOW7">
				<Original>Screw off, I can't help you.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_KNOW1">
				<Original>Yea, I could tell you a thing or two.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_KNOW2">
				<Original>"I think I saw some Syndikat activity, take this.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_KNOW3">
				<Original>Yea, I know some stuff.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_KNOW4">
				<Original>Yea I saw some Syndikat.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_KNOW5">
				<Original>I heard about some Syndikat activity over here.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONE1">
				<Original>I already told you everything I know.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONE2">
				<Original>Don't have anything more for you, sorry.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
			<Key ID="STR_TALK_DONE3">
				<Original>That's all I know.</Original>
				<Russian>да</Russian>
			</Key>
		</Container>

	</Package>
</Project>